<BRANDON HAWLEY>



GAMEPLAY DEVELOPER | C++ | .NET | FULL-STACK

I am a passionate game developer with six years of software development experience in C#, C++, and Java. Specializing in Unity3D and Unreal engine over the past 2 years, I have developed and released multiple titles in each. Recognized for outstanding teamwork, diversity of experience, and a positive approach to every task. I am excited to join my next team and push the boundaries of game design.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Game Developer Intern (Full-Time)

Proper IT Consulting | 4/2023 - 1/2024

- Developed and released multiple games using Unreal Engine and Unity.
- Employed C# and C++ for scripting, game logic, and software creation.
- Utilized Scrum practices with Git systems in a fast-paced development environment

IT Specialist (Contract)

Cumoratek Consulting | 6/2023 - 1/2024

- Managed and maintained student databases, ensuring data integrity and security.
- Enhanced website compatibility and performance.
- Deployed and configured Linux and Windows servers.

Creative Director (Part-Time)

Youtube: ObviouslyBrandon | 1/2022 - Present

- Manage a gaming YouTube channel with a growing subscriber base.
- Gained experience in video editing, script writing, and engagement algorithms.

Business Owner (Full-Time)

Hawleywood Electronics LLC | 1/2018 - 3/2022

- Provided comprehensive computer and electronics repair services.
- Handled all aspects of business operations, including finances and client communication.

General Manager (Full-Time)

Archery Excellence | 5/2016 - 3/2019

- Oversaw event scheduling, employee management, and operational tasks.
- Offered technical support for archery and tech equipment.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

Languages: C#, C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Game Development: Unity, Unreal Engine

3D Modeling: Blender, Maya

Version Control: Git, GitHub, SourceTree

Project Management: Agile/Scrum

Frameworks/Libraries: .NET, Bootstrap, Raylib

Databases: SQL Server, mySQL

Creative Tools: DaVinci Resolve, GIMP, Aseprite

EDUCATION

Certification in Software & Game Development

The Tech Academy | 1/24/2024

· Graduated with honors.

CompTIA A+ Certification

Metropolitan Community College | 12/11/2018

Bachelor of Computer Science (Incomplete)

Metropolitan Community College | 2018 - 2019 *Missouri Western State University* | 2019 - 2020

- Phi-Theta-Kappa Honor Society Member.
- Java Tutor
- Studies cut short due to COVID-19.

For a more details on <u>experience</u> and <u>projects,</u> please visit my *portfolio website*

/GAME/DEVELOPER